Guide to the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Volunteer and Inquirer Correspondence, Series II
  - Older File of Primarily Volunteer Correspondence
    - Minter, H. P. - Mitzner (Box 249, Folder 3075-3084)
    - Mix - Moore, Frank (Box 250, Folder 3085-3095)
    - Moore, Fred - Morrill (Box 251, Folder 3096-3106)
    - Morris - Moss, L. (Box 252, Folder 3107-3118)
    - Moss, R. - Murphy, K. (Box 253, Folder 3119-3131)
    - Murphy, L. - Neal (Box 254, Folder 3132-3142)
    - Neeley - Newell (Box 255, Folder 3143-3150)
    - Newfield - Noland (Box 256, Folder 3151-3161)
    - Norberg - O'Brien (Box 257, Folder 3162-3173)
    - Ockenga - Olson, M. (Box 258, Folder 3174-3184)
    - Olson, N. - Ostrom, H. (Box 259, Folder 3185-3197)
    - Ostrom, W. - Paine (Box 260, Folder 3198-3209)
    - Painter - Parker, Mary A. (Box 261, Folder 3210-3220)
    - Parker, Mary L. - Patton (Box 262, Folder 3221-3231)
    - Paugh - Penner, Elizabeth (Box 263, Folder 3232-3243)
    - Penner, Ella - Peterson, I. (Box 264, Folder 3244-3254)
    - Peterson, J. - Pickren (Box 265, Folder 3255-3264)
    - Pidgeon - Pitts (Box 266, Folder 3265-3275)
    - Place - Pointer (Box 267, Folder 3276-3285)
    - Poling - Pratt (Box 268, Folder 3286-3297)
    - Pray - Pritchard, C. (Box 269, Folder 3298-3307)
    - Pritchard, M. - Quick (Box 270, Folder 3308-3317)
    - Quickel - Rawson (Box 271, Folder 3318-3328)
    - Ray - Rehm (Box 272, Folder 3329-3337)
    - Reich - Reynolds, M. (Box 273, Folder 3338-3348)
    - Reynolds, N. - Ricks (Box 274, Folder 3349-3359)
    - Riddagh - Roberts (Box 275, Folder 3360-3370)
    - Robertson - Rohre (Box 276, Folder 3371-3379)
    - Rohrer - Rost (Box 277, Folder 3380-3390)
    - Rother - Russell, E. (Box 278, Folder 3391-3400)
    - Russell, G. - Salomson (Box 279, Folder 3401-3409)
    - Salser - Sawyer (Box 280, Folder 3410-3419)
    - Saxby - Schnopp (Box 281, Folder 3420-3428)
    - Schoenberg - Scott, C. (Box 282, Folder 3429-3439)
    - Scott, D. - Sedam (Box 283, Folder 3440-3449)
    - Segner - Sharp (Box 284, Folder 3450-3460)
    - Sharpe - Shilling (Box 285, Folder 3461-3468)
    - Shimiau - Simmons (Box 286, Folder 3469-3480)
    - Simms - Sloan (Box 287, Folder 3481-3489)
    - Slocum - Smith, G. (Box 288, Folder 3490-3497)
    - Smith, H. - Smyth (Box 289, Folder 3498-3505)
    - Smythe - Speelman (Box 290, Folder 3506-3513)
    - Speer - Stakes (Box 291, Folder 3514-3523)
    - Staley - Stenger (Box 292, Folder 3524-3535)
    - Stephan - Stiteler (Box 293, Folder 3536-3545)
    - Stjernstrom - Stout (Box 294, Folder 3546-3556)
    - Stovall - Stubbs (Box 295, Folder 3557-3567)
    - Stuck - Swann (Box 296, Folder 3568-3577)
    - Swanson - Talbot, C. (Box 297, Folder 3578-3586)
    - Talbot, G. - Taylor (Box 298, Folder 3587-3596)
    - Tayver - Thomas (Box 299, Folder 3597-3605)
    - Thomas, J. - Thornbloom (Box 300, Folder 3606-3614)
    - Thornburg - Todd (Box 301, Folder 3615-3624)
    - Toews - Trieschmann (Box 302, Folder 3625-3634)
    - Trigg - Tuttle, G. (Box 303, Folder 3635-3644)
    - Tuttle, K. - Van Cronkhite (Cronk), J. E. (Box 304, Folder 3645-3654)
    - Van de Bogart - Vaughan (Box 305, Folder 3655-3664)
    - Vaught - Votaw (Box 306, Folder 3665-3676)
    - Votruba - Walker, M. (Box 307, Folder 3677-3587)
    - Walker, N. - Ward, F. (Box 308, Folder 3688-3699)
    - Ward, H. - Watson, E. (Box 309, Folder 3700-3710)
    - Watson, F. - Weersing (Box 310, Folder 3711-3720)
    - Wees - Welsh (Box 311, Folder 3721-3730)
    - Welshons - Westlake (Box 312, Folder 3731-3740)
    - Weston - Whitcomb, Elmer B. (Box 313, Folder 3741-3749)
    - Whitcomb, Elmer W. - Whitesides (Box 314, Folder 3750-3758)
    - Whitfield - Wilder, G. (Box 315, Folder 3759-3768)
    - Wilder, J. - Williamson, D. (Box 316, Folder 3769-3778)
    - Williamson, E. - Wilson, K. (Box 317, Folder 3779-3789)
    - Wilson, L. - Wintrup (Box 318, Folder 3790-3799)
    - Wise - Wood (Box 319, Folder 3800-3813)
    - Woodard - Wrenn (Box 320, Folder 3814-3828)
    - Wright - Yoder (Box 321, Folder 3829-3843)
    - Yoe - Zemke (Box 322, Folder 3844-3859)
    - Zendt - Zwingle (Box 323, Folder 3860-3868)
  - Older File of Primarily Inquirer Correspondence
    - Abraham - Hayward (Box 324, Folder 3869-3876)
    - Healy - Lyon (Box 325, Folder 3877-3885)
    - Maass - Nute (Box 326, Folder 3886-3892)
    - Oberer - Ryden (Box 327, Folder 3893-3901)
    - Salquist - Tweet (Box 328, Folder 3902-3909)
    - Uhrich - Zoller; Anonymous (Box 329, Folder 3910-3916)
  - More Recent File of Volunteer and Inquirer Correspondence
    Includes Interview Forms and Correspondence
    - Aasland - Barlow (Box 330, Folder 3917-3926)
    - Barnard - Bove (Box 331, Folder 3927-3935)
    - Bowden - Angstrom (Box 332, Folder 3936-3943)
    - Cade - Compton (Box 333, Folder 3944-3954)
    - Condee - DeMolt (Box 334, Folder 3955-3964)
    - Dendz - Ely (Box 335, Folder 3965-3974)
    - Emerson - Freudenberger (Box 336, Folder 3975-3984)
    - Friar - Griswold (Box 337, Folder 3985-3995)
    - Grobe - Helwig (Box 338, Folder 3996-4004)
    - Hemming - Iwig (Box 339, Folder 4005-4013)
    - Jackson - Kint (Box 340, Folder 4014-4023)
    - Kipe - Leeters (Box 341, Folder 4024-4033)
    - Lefferts - McCoy (Box 342, Folder 4034-4042)
    - McCray - Mattison (Box 343, Folder 4043-4052)
    - Mattoon - Morriss (Box 344, Folder 4053-4061)
    - Morrow - Orr (Box 345, Folder 4062-4071)
    - Osborne - Pitts (Box 346, Folder 4072-4081)
    - Plankenhorn - Richter (Box 347, Folder 4082-4094)
    - Riddle - Sayre (Box 348, Folder 4095-4104)
    - Scales - Silvernail (Box 349, Folder 4105-4115)
    - Simes - Stenberg (Box 350, Folder 4116-4126)
    - Stock - Thomas (Box 351, Folder 4127-4137)
    - Thomason - Walenta (Box 352, Folder 4138-4147)
    - Walkden - Willever (Box 353, Folder 4148-4159)
    - Williams - Zwemer (Box 354, Folder 4160-4171)
  - Candidate Department Form Letters and Manuals
    - Form Letters (Box 355, Folder 4172)
    - Manuals, Instructions (Box 355, Folder 4173)
    - Publicity (Box 355, Folder 4174)
    - Miscellany (Box 355, Folder 4175)
- General Correspondence, Series III
  While the correspondence of Series II centers around the individual volunteer or inquirer, the General Correspondence of Series III centers around the life of the Student Volunteer Movement itself - - its policies, operations, and relationships with other organizations. Over seventeen linear feet of letters are organized alphabetically by the name of the person with whom the SVM headquarters staff was corresponding. The arrangement of this Series is somewhat complex due to the fact of a constantly changing headquarters staff and the fact that some of the letters were exchanged between colleagues on the SVM staff.
  The main alphabetical sequence of the Series consists of folders labeled with the names of frequent or notable correspondents. The letters of each individually-noted correspondent are arranged in chronological order. In the cases of leaders of the Movement, the correspondence found in the folders labeled with their names is primarily correspondence from periods when they were not in principal leadership of the Movement. In the case of Robert Wilder, for example, there would be no correspondence arranged under his name for the period 1920 to 1927 when he served as General Secretary of the Movement except with his personal secretaries at the headquarters office. The bulk of correspondence from that period would be filed under the name of the person with whom he, as headquarters staff, was corresponding. When there is correspondence between two SVM staff colleagues the letters are located under the name of the more peripheral staff member. For example, letters exchanged between Executive Chairman John R. Mott and Educational Secretary Harlan P. Beach would be filed under Beach's name.
  Following the alphabetical sequence of frequent or notable correspondents are several brief sequences which represent the routine or less important correspondence of the administrations which led the Movement from 1888 to 1958. No correspondence will be found in these brief sequences for individuals who are listed in the sequence of frequent or notable correspondents. The ten administrations of the SVM were as follows:
  l888-1896: Mott era. During this period before a strong General Secretary position was established, it is considered that John R. Mott was the central leader of the Movement. Toward the latter part of this period H. B. Sharman was designated General Secretary
  1897-1919: Fennell P. Turner administration
  1919-1927: Robert P. Wilder administration
  1927-1936: Jesse R. Wilson administration
  1936: Andrew T. Roy administration (acting General Secretary)
  1937-1940: Paul J. Braisted administration
  1940-1943: R. H. Edwin Espy administration
  1943-1948: Winburn T. Thomas administration
  1948-1954: Edward H. Johnson administration
  1954-1958: Lucius Newton Thurber administration
  In the Turner administration sequence, for example, the SVM correspondents nvolved would include not only General Secretary Turner but also Harlan P. Beach, Burton St. John, William P. McCulloch and other secretaries who served during that period. These less substantive files of each administration are arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - Prominent Correspondents
    - Allison, Anna Lesta, 1949-1952 (Box 356, Folder 4176)
    - Andersen, Hans P., 1899 (Box 356, Folder 4177)
    - Beach, Harlan P., 1895-1897 (Box 356, Folder 4178)
    - Beaver, R. Pierce, 1948-1953 (Box 356, Folder 4185)
    - Borton, J. Harvey, 1924-1935 (Box 356, Folder 4186)
    - Braisted, Paul J., 1937 (Box 356, Folder 4187)
    - Bredenberg, Richard, 1946-1949 (Box 356, Folder 4188)
    - Brockman, Fletcher S., 1894-1941, n.d. (Box 356, Folder 4190)
    - Brooks, Murray, 1927-1935 (Box 356, Folder 4191)
    - Bunch, C. Pardue, 1935-1940 (Box 356, Folder 4192)
    - Campbell, E. Fay, 1915-1919 (Box 357, Folder 4193)
    - Campbell, E. Fay, 1935 (Box 357, Folder 4202)
    - Campbell, E. Fay, 1947-1949 (Box 358, Folder 4206)
    - Capen, Edward Warren, 1907-1913 (Box 358, Folder 4209)
    - Carver, W. O., 1927-1943 (Box 358, Folder 4214)
    - Charrier, Frances B., 1951-1955 (Box 358, Folder 4215)
    - Converse, Paul E., 1949-1951 (Box 358, Folder 4216)
    - Cooley, Frank, 1944,1951-1953 Aug (Box 358, Folder 4218)
    - Coxson, L. D. S., 1930-1934 (Box 359, Folder 4220)
    - Crouch, Archie R., 1932-1954, n.d. (Box 359, Folder 4221)
    - Crutchfield, Margaret see also Roy, Andrew and Margaret, 1922-1926 (Box 359, Folder 4222)
    - Culver, Raymond B., 1927-1930 (Box 359, Folder 4224)
    - Currier, Raymond P., 1930-1946 (Box 359, Folder 4226)
    - Danforth, William H., 1927-1940 (Box 359, Folder 4227)
    - Decker, John W., 1894, 1943 (Box 359, Folder 4228)
    - Donohugh, Thomas S., 1913-1943 (Box 359, Folder 4229)
    - Durham, Eugene, 1927-1938 (Box 359, Folder 4230)
    - Elliott, A. J., 1928-1943 (Box 359, Folder 4231)
    - Elliott, A. Roland, 1930-1935 (Box 359, Folder 4232)
    - Eddy, G. Sherwood, 1894-1895, 1944 (Box 359, Folder 4235)
    - Espy, R. H. Edwin, 1943-1956 (Box 359, Folder 4236)
    - Fahs, Charles, 1895-1946 (Box 360, Folder 4237)
    - Fleming, Daniel H., 1929-1943 (Box 360, Folder 4238)
    - Fraser, Donald, 1894-1896 (Box 360, Folder 4239)
    - Fulton, C. Darby, 1927-1932 (Box 360, Folder 4240)
    - Gowen, Mary Elizabeth, 1948-1951 (Box 360, Folder 4242)
    - Halliday, Vernon, 1910-1923 (Box 360, Folder 4243)
    - Hannum, William H., 1890, 1924-1935 (Box 360, Folder 4245)
    - Harkness, Georgia E., 1927-1944 (Box 360, Folder 4246)
    - Harrison, Paul We, 1929-1938 (Box 360, Folder 4247)
    - Henson, Francis, 1929-1935 (Box 360, Folder 4248)
    - Higdon, E. K., 1937-1954 (Box 360, Folder 4249)
    - Hill, Agnes G., 1894 (Box 360, Folder 4250)
    - Hoffman, Conrad, 1926-1948 (Box 360, Folder 4251)
    - Hoh, David, 1950-1953 (Box 360, Folder 4252)
    - Hoover, Lyman, 1950-1953 (Box 360, Folder 4253)
    - Hunter, John L., 1928-1934 (Box 360, Folder 4254)
    - Inman, S. Guy, 1907-1936 (Box 361, Folder 4256)
    - Jacob, Ernest 0., 1906-1911 (Box 361, Folder 4257)
    - Jessup, Henry Harris, 1894-1895 (Box 361, Folder 4261)
    - Johnson, Edward H., 1944-1947 (Box 361, Folder 4262)
    - Jones, Tracey K., Jr., 1943-1952 (Box 361, Folder 4264)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1917-1923 (Box 361, Folder 4265)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1924 (Box 361, Folder 4266)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1925-1928 (Box 361, Folder 4267)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1930-1931 (Box 361, Folder 4268)
    - Keys, William, 1953- 1957 (Box 362, Folder 4270)
    - Landram, Hughbert H., 1920-1943 (Box 362, Folder 4271)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1906- 1912 (Box 362, Folder 4272)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1913-1914 (Box 362, Folder 4273)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1915-1916 (Box 362, Folder 4274)
    - Lerrigo, P. H. J., 1926-1938 (Box 362, Folder 4283)
    - Lobenstine, Edwin C., 1916-1937 (Box 362, Folder 4284)
    - Luce, Henry T., 1894-1895 (Box 362, Folder 4285)
    - Lyon, D. Willard, 1894-1937 (Box 363, Folder 4286)
    - McCulloch, William P., 1918-1921 (Box 363, Folder 4287)
    - Mackay, John A., 1927-1935 (Box 363, Folder 4289)
    - MacMillan, Hugh A., 1920-1923 (Box 363, Folder 4293)
    - Markley, Mary E., 1929-1937 (Box 363, Folder 4296)
    - Miller, David V., 1950 (Box 363, Folder 4298)
    - Morgan, William H., 1908-1938 (Box 363, Folder 4300)
    - Morton, Helen, 1936-1944 (Box 363, Folder 4301)
    - Moss, Leslie B., 1929-1933 (Box 364, Folder 4302)
    - Mott, John R., 1898-1918 (Box 364, Folder 4305)
    - Mott, John R., 1931-1932 (Box 364, Folder 4309)
    - Mott, John R., 1933 (Box 364, Folder 4310)
    - Mott, John R., 1936-1940 (Box 364, Folder 4312)
    - Murray, John A., 1925- 1934 (Box 365, Folder 4314)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1907-1908Aug (Box 365, Folder 4315)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1908May-Dec (Box 365, Folder 4316)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1909-1910 Jun (Box 365, Folder 4317)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1910Jun- 1911 (Box 365, Folder 4318)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1924 (Box 366, Folder 4328)
    - Murray, William D., 1899-1932 (Box 366, Folder 4335)
    - National Council of Young Men's Christian Associations, 1922-1937 (Box 366, Folder 4337)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1929-1934 (Box 366, Folder 4338)
    - Oldham, J. H., 1923-1936 (Box 366, Folder 4339)
    - Parlin, Elwyn C., 1930-1935 (Box 366, Folder 4340)
    - Parsons, Artley B., 1927-1938 (Box 366, Folder 4341)
    - Paton, William, 1926-1935 (Box 366, Folder 4342)
    - Penfield, Thornton B., 1906-1917 (Box 367, Folder 4343)
    - Pier, Stanhope R., 1922-1932 (Box 367, Folder 4346)
    - Pieters, Albertus, 1927-1932 (Box 367, Folder 4347)
    - Pilkin, Horace T., 1894-1895 (Box 367, Folder 4348)
    - Porter, David R. (Box 367, Folder 4349)
    - Poteat, Gordon, 1910-1921 (Box 367, Folder 4356)
    - Puxley, H. L., 1937 (Box 368, Folder 4358)
    - Robbins, Joseph C., 1910-1913 (Box 368, Folder 4359)
    - Robbins, Joseph C., 1916-1919 (Box 368, Folder 4361)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1913-1928 (Box 368, Folder 4364)
    - Rossman, G. Parker, 1944-1948 (Box 368, Folder 4365)
    - Rossman, Vernon, 1949 (Box 368, Folder 4366)
    - Rowland, Wilmina, 1933 (Box 368, Folder 4369)
    - Rowland, Wilmina, 1935 Aug-Dec (Box 369, Folder 4373)
    - Roy, Andrew T., 1921-1927 (Box 369, Folder 4379)
    - Roy, Andrew T. and Margaret C. (see also: Crutchfield, Margaret), 1928-1934 (Box 369, Folder 4380)
    - Rutherford, Gertrude, 1924-1933 (Box 369, Folder 4383)
    - Sailer, T. H. P., 1906-1911 (Box 369, Folder 4385)
    - St. John, Burton and Io, 1906-1917 (Box 370, Folder 4387)
    - Sanders, Frank Knight, 1895 (Box 370, Folder 4392)
    - Sayre, Francis B., 1937-1952 (Box 370, Folder 4393)
    - Sewell, H. Burton, 1932-1933 (Box 370, Folder 4394)
    - Sharman, H. B., 1894-1897 (Box 370, Folder 4395)
    - Sharp, Thomas S., 1906-1910 (Box 370, Folder 4396)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1911-1913 (Box 370, Folder 4397)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1914-1917 (Box 370, Folder 4398)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1918-1919 (Box 370, Folder 4399)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1920-1921 (Box 370, Folder 4400)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1922-1923 (Box 370, Folder 4401)
    - Sharp, Thomas S, 1924-1929 (Box 370, Folder 4402)
    - Shedd, Clarence P., 1925-1951 (Box 371, Folder 4403)
    - Soper, Edmund D., 1922-1944 (Box 371, Folder 4404)
    - Speer, Robert E., 1894-1912 (Box 371, Folder 4405)
    - Speers, James M., 1907-1912 (Box 371, Folder 4410)
    - Speers, James M., 1913-1925 (Box 371, Folder 4411)
    - Speers, James M., 1926-1932 (Box 371, Folder 4412)
    - Speers, James M., 1933-1936 (Box 371, Folder 4413)
    - Stauffer, Milton, 1922-1924 (Box 372, Folder 4416)
    - Stevenson, J. Ross, 1895-1912 (Box 372, Folder 4421)
    - Stewart, George, 1925-1939 (Box 372, Folder 4424)
    - Storm, Harold, 1930-1939 (Box 372, Folder 4425)
    - Taylor, W. E., 1912-1927 (Box 372, Folder 4426)
    - Ting, K. H., 1949-1950 (Box 372, Folder 4427)
    - Tucker, Luther, 1931-1938 (Box 372, Folder 4428)
    - Turner, Fennell P., 1919-1921 (Box 372, Folder 4430)
    - Turner, Fennell P, 1925 (Box 373, Folder 4433)
    - Van Dusen, Henry P., 1927-1934 (Box 373, Folder 4435)
    - Varker, William and Mary, 1920-1926 (Box 373, Folder 4437)
    - Visser 't Hooft, Willem A., 1929-1938 (Box 373, Folder 4439)
    - Wallace, Cornelia, 1927-1929 (Box 373, Folder 4440)
    - Walters, Orville S., 1922-1926 (Box 373, Folder 4443)
    - Warnshuis, Abbe Livingston, 1912-1923 (Box 373, Folder 4445)
    - Wasson, Alfred W., 1927-1937 (Box 374, Folder 4448)
    - Weigle, Luther A., 1930-1941 (Box 374, Folder 4449)
    - White, J. Campbell, 1907-1910 (Box 374, Folder 4450)
    - Wilder, Robert P., 1907-1911 (Box 374, Folder 4455)
    - Wilson, Jesse R., 1914-1918 (Box 374, Folder 4463)
    - Wilson, Jesse R., 1921Jan-Apr (Box 374, Folder 4466)
    - Wilson, Jesse R., 1922-1924 (Box 375, Folder 4468)
    - Wilson, Jesse R., 1926 0ct- 1927 May (Box 375, Folder 4472)
    - Wilson, Jesse R., 1936 Jul- 1938 (Box 375, Folder 4474)
    - Wygal, Winifred, 1922-1927 (Box 375, Folder 4475)
    - Young, Herrick B., 1936-1939 (Box 375, Folder 4478)
    - Young, Herrick B., 1947-1949 (Box 375, Folder 4479)
    - Young Women's Christian Association, 1929-1940 (Box 375, Folder 4481)
    - Zwemer, Samuel M., 1907-1913 (Box 376, Folder 4482)
    - Zwemer, Samuel M., 1930 (Box 376, Folder 4491)
  - Administration Correspondence
    - Mott Era
      - Addy-Fitch (Box 377, Folder 4495)
      - Gardner-Kissack (Box 377, Folder 4496)
      - Lawrence-Stock (Box 377, Folder 4497)
      - Taylor - Young Men of India; anonymous (Box 377, Folder 4498)
    - Turner Administration
      - Calder-Moore (Box 377, Folder 4499)
    - Wilder Administration
      - Amherst College - Burgess (Box 377, Folder 4500)
      - Chao - Cunard (Box 377, Folder 4501)
      - Danner - Fry (Box 377, Folder 4502)
      - Gaebelein - Gwinn (Box 377, Folder 4503)
      - Heibert - Irving (Box 377, Folder 4504)
      - Johnston - Lowe (Box 377, Folder 4505)
      - McAmmand - Morgenthau (Box 377, Folder 4506)
      - Nathan - Prentice (Box 377, Folder 4507)
      - Ritter - Tupper (Box 377, Folder 4508)
      - VanBlarcom - Zerby (Box 377, Folder 4509)
    - Wilson Administration
      - Aaron - Adeva (Box 377, Folder 4510)
      - Agne - Alexander (Box 377, Folder 4511)
      - Allen - Anderson (Box 377, Folder 4512)
      - Applegath - Arnup (Box 377, Folder 4513)
      - Aslin - Auclair (Box 378, Folder 4514)
      - Babcock - Baxter (Box 378, Folder 4515)
      - Beall - Berry (Box 378, Folder 4516)
      - Bible - Bitzer (Box 378, Folder 4517)
      - Black - Blanchard (Box 378, Folder 4518)
      - Blein - Bonsall (Box 378, Folder 4519)
      - Booth - Bowden (Box 378, Folder 4520)
      - Braden - Brethorst (Box 378, Folder 4521)
      - Briggs - Burkhart (Box 378, Folder 4522)
      - Bustamante - Byrum (Box 378, Folder 4523)
      - Cadman - Canon (Box 378, Folder 4524)
      - Carleton - Carty (Box 378, Folder 4525)
      - Case - Cavert (Box 378, Folder 4526)
      - Central - Chapin (Box 378, Folder 4527)
      - Charlesworth - Christian (Box 378, Folder 4528)
      - Clark - Blanche (Box 378, Folder 4529)
      - Coates - Corlies (Box 379, Folder 4530)
      - Craft - Crutchfield (Box 379, Folder 4531)
      - Currie - Cuyugan (Box 379, Folder 4532)
      - Dalton - Day (Box 379, Folder 4533)
      - DeChant - Delaware (Box 379, Folder 4534)
      - Dickerson - Downs (Box 379, Folder 4535)
      - Drake - Dwinell (Box 379, Folder 4536)
      - Eastman - Eitzen (Box 379, Folder 4537)
      - Elske - Emergency Work Bureau (Box 379, Folder 4538)
      - Endo - Ewald (Box 379, Folder 4539)
      - F. Whiting, Inc. - Fetters (Box 379, Folder 4540)
      - Field - Fitt (Box 379, Folder 4541)
      - Fleckles - Franklin (Box 379, Folder 4542)
      - Fraser - Funk (Box 379, Folder 4543)
      - G. E. Stechert - Gay (Box 379, Folder 4544)
      - Geisler - Gossard (Box 380, Folder 4545)
      - Grafton - Grove (Box 380, Folder 4546)
      - Gulley - Gwinn (Box 380, Folder 4547)
      - Haddad - Hallman (Box 380, Folder 4548)
      - Hammaker - Hand (Box 380, Folder 4549)
      - Harbison (Box 380, Folder 4550)
      - Harper - Harrowell (Box 380, Folder 4551)
      - Hart - Hayes (Box 380, Folder 4552)
      - Hearn - Heydon (Box 380, Folder 4553)
      - Hicks - Hines (Box 380, Folder 4554)
      - Hobart - Hoh (Box 380, Folder 4555)
      - Hollinger - Hsiao (Box 380, Folder 4556)
      - Huckabee - Huntley (Box 380, Folder 4557)
      - Hurrey - Hylbert (Box 380, Folder 4558)
      - Igler - Ives (Box 380, Folder 4559)
      - Jabavu - Jenness (Box 381, Folder 4560)
      - Johnson - Junkin (Box 381, Folder 4561)
      - Kagawa - Kennedy (Box 381, Folder 4562)
      - Kidde - Knight (Box 381, Folder 4563)
      - Kocher - Kyle (Box 381, Folder 4564)
      - Lacey - Laughton (Box 381, Folder 4565)
      - Lavender (Box 381, Folder 4566)
      - Leavell - Liu (Box 381, Folder 4567)
      - Lock - Longenecker (Box 381, Folder 4568)
      - Lotz - McCurdy (Box 381, Folder 4569)
      - Macdonald - McGregor (Box 381, Folder 4570)
      - Mack - McMillan (Box 381, Folder 4571)
      - Madison - Martin (Box 381, Folder 4572)
      - Matheson - Mays (Box 382, Folder 4573)
      - Medlock - Mickle (Box 382, Folder 4574)
      - Miley - Minter (Box 382, Folder 4575)
      - Mohican Press - Mutch (Box 382, Folder 4576)
      - National City Realty Corp. - Owen (Box 382, Folder 4577)
      - Padelford - Parkinson (Box 382, Folder 4578)
      - Paschal - Paul (Box 382, Folder 4579)
      - Peace Films Foundation - Peddie School (Box 382, Folder 4580)
      - Pellegin - Phillips (Box 382, Folder 4581)
      - Pickell - Powers (Box 382, Folder 4582)
      - The Presbyterian Banner - Quillian (Box 382, Folder 4583)
      - Rainey - Rawlings (Box 382, Folder 4584)
      - Reader's Digest - Reynolds (Box 382, Folder 4585)
      - Riddle - Ruxton (Box 382, Folder 4586)
      - Salters - Scott (Box 382, Folder 4587)
      - Seabury - Skinkle (Box 382, Folder 4588)
      - Slack - Starling (Box 383, Folder 4589)
      - Stedman - Stone (Box 383, Folder 4590)
      - Story - Strong (Box 383, Folder 4591)
      - Sunday - Swenson (Box 383, Folder 4592)
      - Tarkington - Theodore (Box 383, Folder 4593)
      - Thomas - Tinker (Box 383, Folder 4594)
      - Tobias - Towner (Box 383, Folder 4595)
      - Tracy - Tweel (Box 383, Folder 4596)
      - Uphous - Voris (Box 383, Folder 4597)
      - Waddell - Wawayanda Conference Center (Box 383, Folder 4598)
      - Weatherbee - White (Box 383, Folder 4599)
      - Wiggin - Wilson (Box 383, Folder 4600)